### **NANDAN KUMAR HG**

+39 3472809168 | Via Curzola 10, Padova, Italy 35135

<u>nandanhg2222@gmail.com</u> | <u>www.linkedin.com/in/nandan-kumar-hg-42884b184</u> portfolio: https://nandanhg.github.io/portfolio.github.io

### **SUMMARY**

Analyst with over 2 years of full time work experience in analyzing, designing data and creating aircraft technical documentation. A team player and a highly motivated individual willing to learn new technologies. Able to adapt to different work culture and always ready to accept new challenges.

### **SKILLS**

- Qlik sense
- Tableau
- Power BI
- SAP MM
- JIRA
- AutoCAD
- Catiav5

- HTML
- CSS
- Figma
- JavaScript
- ISO draw
- UI/UX design
- Web design
- Arbotextepic editor
- Adobe premiere pro
- Adobe Illustrator
- Project management
- Digital marketing
  - Technical writing
- Technical service

### **EDUCATION**

### Masters in Engineering Management

Universita degli studi di Padova, Italy

Bachelors in Mechanical Engineering

Aug 2015 – Jul 2019

Oct 2021 - Jun 2023

Vishvesvarayya Technological University, East Point collage of Engineering, Bengaluru, India CGPA: 8.22 out of 10

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **BRAINNEST Business Consulting and Services, Bremen, Germany Project Management Trainee**

May 2022 – Jun 2022

Part of the project management team, responsible for planning, execution, monitoring, controlling and closing out projects. My responsibilities include:

- Coordination and supervision of project from the kick-off to close-out.
- Analyzing stakeholder's expectations.
- Prioritizing and planning the product backlog and sprint backlogs.

- Analyzing and assorting project risks by maintaining risk register regarding minimizing risk.
- Establishing and maintaining a constant stream of communication between different departments of the project for efficient functioning.
- Used agile methodologies, with specific reference to the scrum framework in JIRA.

# CAPGEMINI CONSULTING INDIA PVT LTD, BANGALORE, INDIA Analyst

Aug 2019 - Sep 2021

Part of the team responsible for developing and maintaining aircraft technical documentations and project dashboard creations. My responsibilities included:

- Writing aircraft maintenance procedures and descriptions in various ATA chapters for AMM, AIPC, CMM, SRM, ITEM and TLMC manuals (Technical documentation).
- Providing technical service for Aircraft Maintenance Technicians.
- Data visualization, creating dashboards using tableau.

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Qlik Sense Business Analyst Qualification.

### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Italian (Beginner)

### **HOBBIES**

- Portrait pencil sketching
- Photography

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in this application to be processed for the purposes of current and future recruitment processes.